The capitol of Ostania, Berlint.
This old woman is a contact for
Westalis's intelligence agency, WISE.
This man's name is Loid Forger,
otherwise known by his code name, Twilight.
His occupation: spy.
It appears as though, on top of the current
important mission he is conducting,
he's been given another.
This has been my life for decades now.
Every day remains the same,
and peace is fleeting.
Will we ever see a day
when we're not needed anymore?
Mission complete.
Good day, or perhaps, good evening, Twilight.
We thank you for completing
that mission so quickly.
How goes Operation Strix?
That is his top-priority mission to maintain
peace between the East and the West.
That mission...
It's going smoothly.
I have secured both a wife and child.
...is meant to bring the enemy
country's plans for war to light,
establish a family in said country,
and infiltrate a certain academy.
Very good. Not standing out is
an iron-clad rule for a spy.
Continue acting as a
completely mundane family.
I know.
Did you quit smoking?
Well, I have a child now.
And thus, the Forgers came
to be without issue, but...
Loid did mention that he
was going to be late,
so why don't we eat out tonight?
Yep.
Doctors sure are busy. It must be difficult.
Papa is not actually a doctor.
His daughter, Anya, whom he just happened
to adopt from an orphanage...
Papa's real job is a spy.
Today, he went to take down an arms dealer.
...is an Esper who can read minds.
I bring you my dish!
Thank you very much, Miss Anya.
Hmm... It's just not washing off...
His wife, Yor, who agreed to this arrangement
because of a common interest...
I can still smell the blood
from yesterday's kill.
...is a hardcore assassin.
A spy, a telepath, and an assassin.
The three decided to live under one roof
for their own reasons while
concealing their true identities,
and so their less-than-mundane
family life continues on.
PENGUIN PARK
I keep getting all these extra missions
every day, on top of Operation Strix.
HQ must be in dire straits
over the personnel shortage.
When I get home, I have my
pretend family to deal with.
I am an agent. Therefore,
my soul has no time to rest.
Hey, don't you think the husband
across the hall must be in trouble?
It's supposed to be a day off, but he's
working late into the night again.
They're our neighbors...
And they have a little child.
That poor, neglected thing.
I rarely see the three of them together.
He's probably off cheating somewhere!
How awful!
Maybe he actually got fired,
and he can't bring himself to go home.
I was careless.
I was so consumed by my other missions
that I neglected playing
the role of the father well.
Even the slightest suspicion or mistrust
from those around us in a deception operation
can be detrimental.
I must do everything I can
to remedy this situation.
A threat to our family is
a threat to the world!
We're going out next weekend!
The three of us will have a good time.
Where do we want to go?
Oh? Is that a penguin, Anya?
I know. Let's go to the aquarium.
Um... You seem exhausted.
Why not get some rest?
Yor, in order for our pretend
marriage to continue,
we must do everything we can to
seem like a normal, happy family.
So look forward to the weekend!
So exciting!
I need to take care of all of
my other missions before then.
Well... let's go.
Loid, perhaps you really
should get some rest.
I'm perfectly fine.
Oh, if it isn't the Forgers.
It's so rare to see all of you together.
We're about to go enjoy some
time together at the aquarium.
Isn't that exciting, Anya?
I see...
We need to show our neighbors
what a happy family we are
so they don't ever suspect
that we're a pretend family.
My papa, who is taking us on an ooting,
and my mama, who is very kind to
my papa, are both very good people.
I think our family is completely normal.
That sounded more like an explanation
than anything else, but good enough.
Now, then...
If you'll excuse us.
Please wait, Papa, who is a
very good and normal person!
Ba-donk ka-chonk!
Another summons?
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'm going to go buy us some drinks.
All right.
Agent Twilight, we've got another
additional mission for you tod—
I cannot.
This is straight from WISE HQ—
I cannot. Today is a very
important day for Operation Strix.
Papa!
We need to hurry, or the
aquarium will go out of business!
Don't worry, they just remodeled the place.
Just wait patiently.
There you have it.
Anyway, I'll take one coffee, one juice—
Hang on! Did you say "aquarium"?
Splendid, Agent Twilight.
The location of this mission just
happens to be Berlint Aquarium!
I am blown away at how prepared you are!
No, really. This was a coincidence.
Could I get that coffee and juice now?
There will be some intel
traded at the aquarium—
My coffee and juice, please.
Listen to me carefully, Twilight.
This intel contains instructions from another
country for making a new chemical weapon.
If terrorists get their
hands on this information,
many will perish in our country!
So many... fishies!
An octopus!
Starfish.
A tiny shark!
She looks like she's having fun.
Loid...
You look so pale. Are you all right?
I ended up taking the mission.
But we did successfully show the
neighbors how well we get along.
As long as I can get through
this separate mission...
Oh, if it isn't the Forgers
from across the hall.
What a coincidence.
Oh, hello.
You can't... be serious!
We just got here, too.
Now I definitely can't relax.
Actually, we just need
to shoo them off, and—
Would you like to join us?
Yor!
What a great idea.
Papa is funny.
If we want to appear normal,
we need to keep up a good
relationship with our neighbors.
Very well, then.
I'll take care of this mission immediately,
and then return to weekend mode.
According to our intel,
they smuggled in a capsule containing
film by making a penguin swallow it.
Why a penguin?
It was brought in sometime
yesterday at an unknown time.
The recipient has not appeared yet.
You must retrieve the goods before the
enemy organization does, no matter what!
Why don't we check out the penguin exhibit?
It seems to be the main attraction.
Okay.
I like penguins! I wanna see!
Welcome to the world's biggest penguin park!
P-P-P-Penguins!
Our most recommended
attraction at this aquarium
is our adorable underwater show
that stars 200 penguins!
Exactly which penguin is my target?
There's no time to check
each and every penguin.
I'd have a better chance of stopping the
terrorist from obtaining the film...
No... Since I don't know when
the recipient is going to show up,
that'll be difficult, as well.
I won't be able to keep an eye
on all of these penguins alone.
What am I going to do?
There has to be something...
They must've marked the penguin somehow
to tell it apart from the others.
Papa is troubled.
Loid is so enthusiastic. I guess he lets
his inner child out sometimes, too.
Hey, that fish looks tasty.
Wait, where did my kid go?!
I hope my girlfriend stops being so angry.
Fish...
It's hard to read the minds of penguins.
Let's play.
I'mma eat some fish.
I'm hungry.
Come over here.
Papa, that penguin looks like it can't breathe.
It's drinking a lot of water
only to spit it all back out.
It's possible there's something
stuck in its throat.
This is definitely worth investigating.
Sorry. I'm going to go buy
some drinks real quick.
Loid... His exhaustion must
be making him so thirsty.
Hey! Where's the new guy
we're supposed to get today?
He's this late on his first day?
Sorry I'm late!
What's wrong with you young'uns today?
I'll show you how to feed
the penguins. Follow me.
Yes, sir!
The fastest way to get closer to the target
penguin without causing a commotion
is to disguise myself as
one of the aquarists.
Agent Twilight's Specialty: Disguises
The first thing a newbie has to learn
is all of the penguins' faces and names.
Did you memorize the roster?
Yes. I glanced through it
quickly in the staff room.
You glanced through? You moron!
Even with me, it took two
years to learn all 200...
Oh, Chief. You're about to step
on poor Petilda behind you.
This is indeed Petilda.
This one is Pemas, and this is Pescar.
How can you tell, newbie?
Huh? Well, all of their patterns
are completely different.
Their faces and heights, too.
Even I still mistake them
every once in a while.
I can't believe this guy's
observation skills and memory.
All right, then. Let's get to feeding them.
This way.
The penguin I spotted earlier is...
Right there. Parles, the emperor penguin.
I need to get to him immediately and...
Wh-Wha?!
I-I can't go any further.
We've got big eaters and fussy eaters.
Each penguin has unique
eating habits, so pay attention.
I don't have time for this.
I need to hurry back, or the
neighbors will be suspicious.
Chief!
Allow me to do the honors!
What?
I figured this out watching
veteran aquarists...
The most important thing
is how each penguin eats.
How much they eat, what kind of food it is,
and where each group is located.
As long as I can figure these things out...
Controlling the masses is mere child's play.
That's no ordinary newbie!
Uh-oh. Apparently Parles isn't very hungry.
He might be sick, so I'll take
him to the treatment room.
If you'll excuse me for a bit.
S-Sure...
Sorry, little guy.
Bingo! There's something
stuck in his throat.
Upon closer observation, it seems there's
a mark on the bottom of his foot, too.
Just a second, little guy.
I'll get it out for you.
You there.
What are you planning to
do with that penguin?
He's not feeling well, so I'm
taking him to the treatment room.
I see. Allow me to do that for you.
I'm terribly sorry. Only staff
are allowed to handle them.
My apologies.
I'm a professor from Berlint University's
marine biology research lab.
I'm in charge of the marine animals here.
This ID is fake.
It's not even well-made.
Who do you work for, you—
You're not getting away!
Hey, be still!
Hey, newbie!
Where are you taking that penguin?
The treatment room is that way!
I can't carelessly let him go without
knowing how many enemies are here.
My top priority is retrieving this film.
I'll have to give up on chasing after him.
Oh, no... Now where did
Miss Anya run off to?
I need to let my comrades
outside know to kill that man,
and retrieve the film—
Who the hell are you?!
Mama! I'm being kidnapped!
Miss Anya?!
Let go of me!
What are you talking ab—
What do you think...
you're doing to my daughter?!
Wow.
Are you all right?
Oh, no. I definitely overdid it.
I hope he's not dead...
Wow.
And so, Twilight was able to retrieve the film
and get information about the enemy
organization from the man they captured.
You know, your husband
hasn't come back at all.
I'm telling you, he's cheating!
How awful!
Huh? That's not...
I'm sorry I took so long!
Loid!
Ta-da!
A penguin!
Oh, what a big stuffed penguin!
Where did you get it?
It was a prize from the penguin name-guessing
challenge they were doing over there.
I just had to get it for Anya,
so I kept trying over and over.
Boy, it sure was difficult.
Papa is a liar. He actually got it in one try.
He got so worked up. How adorable.
You're a better father than I thought.
I'm impressed.
You flatter me.
I'm just a simple father trying
not to stumble around too much
It's bigger than you, Miss Anya.
as I protect my happy little family.
Now that I've gotten a closer look
at you, you're quite handsome.
Looks like things are going
to work out here, too.
But I'm absolutely done with
all this excessive overwork.
I'm going to file a complaint to
HQ and request a long vaca—
No...
Maintaining a world where
children don't cry...
A world with no war...
That is my duty.
I have no time to stand by idly.
Papa! The dolphin show is gonna start!
Sorry, could you walk a little slower?
What?! You want me to be the chief?!
But why?!
I have nothing more to teach you.
I am Director Chimera, the boss
of the secret organization P2.
So you're the new recruit, eh?
I am called Penguin, please,
and I come from the aquarium.
It is a pweasure to meet
your acquaintenance.
Indeed.
Agent Anya, you know what to do.
Yep!
We have a ritual in which we both
eat the halves of a split peanut.
Once you have completed this task,
you will be officially recognized
as a member of this organization.
Om...
Starting today, you will be
known as Agent Penguinman.
Do your best for peace.
Yep.
Agent Anya, show our new
agent around our hideout.
Okey-dokey!
This is our hideout's command room.
We gather intel from this machine every day.
* She watches cartoons
This is Agent Papa. He is a
super-elite that can do anything.
Um... what? Is she pretending to be a spy?
This is Agent Mama.
She's strong, but fails at everything else.
Am I that much of a failure?!
They are Anya's trusted lackeys.
Okay, onward to the next spot.
It looks like Miss Anya has taken
quite a liking to that plushie.
Mm...
This is the bathroom!
You can heal your wounds from battle here.
This is Anya's room. I train in here every day.
* She studies
And...
The most top-secret spots in our hideout.
Papa's room and Mama's room!
Be on your guard.
If you discover the secret of
these rooms, you won't leave alive.
We might find the ultimate knife,
or the ultimate bomb!
Now, then...
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
How many times have I told you not
to go in there without permission?!
Er, it's just, there's a lot of dangerous things
in there, like scissors and heaters.
Honestly, there are far more
dangerous things in there.
Yes, you shouldn't go in mine, either.
My room has poisoned needles and such.
Papa and Mama, I hate you both!
Anya's gonna run away from home!
Not good. At this rate,
Operation Strix is going to collapse!
What should I do?
A-Agent Anya!
There's no time for crying!
World peace is on the line!
L-Let's wrap up the tour of the hideout
and head out for our next mission!
Y-Yes! Let's go beat the bad guys!
Okay! Follow me, you two!
The bad guys have taken over
the candy store on 2nd Street.
Let's go save them!
Huh?
Be careful.
The enemy might have set traps.
W-Well done, Agent Anya.
What is that?
Aw, what a sweet family.
A spy must not stand out...
Later on, Anya's mood improved
after they bought her a snack,
and peace was restored
to the Forger household.